we believe in cement abduction the rock
you can see that big thing in a
captain's the detail details included in
SMI don't leave hopefully show victim
very high-tech although hailed a
complete Pacific moisture to they did
with a little contact I wouldn't show
weakness
technique people to them 15 years
- SMI they you do captain so hard I
potentially Tasha
[Music]
- toy in conduit into my business that's
a voice a day compared we can tell that
made for you to be infected by licking
your dhoti die Prudential Vietnam
[Music]
directive SMI pattern Emily I have to
kangaroo but it'll go sunshine the
included ot to go if a file company to
deploy this against the way
to Detroit to Toyota
Shia fashion shy they might eat tonight
- so that we feed them to told happy
[Applause]
[Music]
okay objectively typically you can get
you my dear to go down fighting
a tonight
a
little help level could be motivated
predation signal
judicial mm
we could excited
LT Michigan puja boy
thank you Tony I don't come anyway God
is in
[Music]
the tentacles and computo people up
though
[Music]
[Applause]